{
    "subject": "resource/Sussex_Skyhawks",
    "predicate": "property/title",
    "object": "Sussex Skyhawks",
    "human_readable": "The title of Sussex Skyhawks is Sussex Skyhawks.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9856955409049988,
            "question": "What is the title of Sussex Skyhawks?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9510769248008728,
            "question": "Is Sussex Skyhawks a team name?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9238820672035217,
            "question": "Is 'Sussex Skyhawks' a common name?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9076746106147766,
            "question": "What sport might 'Sussex Skyhawks' play?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.883840799331665,
            "question": "What do we call 'Sussex Skyhawks'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8485271334648132,
            "question": "Where do you think 'Sussex Skyhawks' are from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4783779978752136,
            "question": "Do you know any teams with the name 'Skyhawks'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4746023416519165,
            "question": "Is 'Sussex' a place name?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.05053522437810898,
            "question": "Can you tell me the name of the team?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.014969977550208569,
            "question": "Are there other teams with similar names?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The title of Sussex Skyhawks is Sussex Skyhawks.",
            "html": "dbpedia_6255_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you tell me the name of the team?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6255_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is 'Sussex' a place name?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6255_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Do you know any teams with the name 'Skyhawks'?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6255_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6255_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6255_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6255_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6255_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6255_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6255_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6255_30.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6255_38.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6255_50.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6255_52.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents provided contain information about the Sussex Skyhawks, including their official name as stated. Therefore, the triple \"The title of Sussex Skyhawks is Sussex Skyhawks\" is supported by the given context."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {'output': 'yes'}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}